MARISKA Adriaanzen

BSC IT student



About Me

Creative and driven programmer with 4 years of experience in coding and customer service, gained through university and work. I'm confident working both independently and in a team, with experience managing multiple projects and delivering quality results on time.

Skills:

Java

Project Management Python Team Coordination

Effective C#/ C++

Communication Time SQL

Management Critical HTML

Thinking MATLAB

Education:

BSC IT 2023 - Present BSC Physics and Mathematics 2022 - 2023 (Incomplete) Matric 2021

Language:

Afrikaans English German



+081 359 3431

Mariska Adriaanzen Virtual CV

Krugersdorp, Gauteng, South Africa

Professional Experience:

Waitress

April 2021 - January 2022 | Jolly Roger

Runner

November 2019 - December 2020 | Founders Grill

Hostess

November 2019 - January 2022 | Doppio Zero

Multi-role Assistant

November 2023 - Present | Kaatfoot

Education:

- · National Senior Certificate: 2021
- BSC Physics and Mathematics: 2022
 - 2023 (Incomplete)
- BSC Information Technology: 2023 -Present

References:

- Timothy (Doppio Zero 067 117 3900
- Liezl Van Onselen(Jolly Roger) 076 149 6383
- Elen Roux(SACOPA and WACOPA) 083 626 6512
- Narine Kruger (Kaalfööt) 083 969 1312